departures.com 2014-11-23

# Privacy Statement

Effective Date: September 12, 2014

Time Inc. Affluent Media Group ("TIAMG," "we," "our" or "us"), a subsidiary of Time Inc., is committed to safeguarding your privacy. We want you to know how we may collect, use, share, and keep information about you and the choices that are available to you. Click here for a list of the businesses that are governed by this Privacy Policy.

This online privacy policy applies to TIAMG sites, applications, products, publications and services that reference this policy. 

Our sites, applications, products, publications and services are not intended for children under 13 years of age. We do not knowingly solicit data online from, or market online to, children under 13 years of age. 

Since we may change this online privacy policy from time to time, we recommend that you check the current version available. 

## What is in this online privacy policy?

  * What information does this online privacy policy cover?
  * What information do we collect and how do we collect it?
  * How do we use the information we collect about you?
  * Your California Privacy Rights: Notice to California Customers
  * How do we share your information?
    * How we treat your Personal Information
    * How we handle aggregate and de-identified information
  * How do we keep and safeguard your information?
  * What are your choices?
  * Collection of Information by Third-Party Sites and Sponsors
  * How we serve advertising
  * Accessing, Correcting, and Deleting Your Personal Information
  * How to Contact Us
  * TIAMG

##   
What information does this online privacy policy cover?

This online privacy policy describes how we (and our Service Providers) may collect, use, share, and keep information that we get about you. We gather Online Information, which is data or information collected on the TIAMG sites and applications as well as on sites and applications of third parties relating to topics about our business, and Other Information, which is TIAMG internal information (for example subscription transaction data), external data used to process transactions and other online and offline data, including data collected from or about you via telephone, postal mail, in person and from Business Partners.

We gather Online Information and Other Information if you:

  * Visit or use our sites, applications, products, publications or services;
  * Order publications or other products;
  * Receive or reply to communications from us; 
  * View or click on our ads or engage with other online content or in various activities like entering contests or sweepstakes, playing games, taking quizzes, voting in polls or otherwise expressing an opinion; subscribe to one of our services, such as newsletters; or participate in one of our online forums or communities; and
  * Interact with us through social media sites and other sites and applications

In this policy, we also explain how we may combine Online Information and Other Information we collect from you and how we then use the combined information. 

##   
What information do we collect and how do we collect it?

The types of information we collect depends on which product or service you use.

Sometimes you give information directly to us (or to our Service Providers). For example, you might give us your name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, date of birth and credit or debit card information in order to:

  * Subscribe to or purchase any of our products or services, such as our publications or club memberships; 
  * Fill out a form or survey;
  * Give us information for consideration for content on a website or in a magazine or application. This might include writing an essay, taking photographs or videos, and other activities. 
  * Register, log into or update the settings on your account using our online services;
  * Enter a competition or register for a marketing offer; or
  * Buy something on our sites and in our applications. 

At some TIAMG sites and through certain promotions, you can submit information about other people. For example, you might submit a person's name, mailing and/or e-mail address to send a gift or electronic greeting card. The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected about other people at these pages include recipient's name, address, e-mail address and telephone number.

We (and our Service Providers or Third-Party Ad-Servers) also collect information through Cookies and Similar Technologies. Most Cookies and Similar Technologies will only collect De-Identified Information such as how you arrive at our website or your general location. However, certain Cookies and Similar Technologies do collect Personal Information. For example, if you click Remember Me when you log in to our website, a cookie will store your information. 

We (and our Service Providers or Third-Party Ad-Servers) may collect information using Cookies and Similar Technologies about:

  * The device you use to browse our sites (for example, we may collect information about the operating system or the browser version and the type of computer or mobile device, including other identifying details);
  * The IP Address and information related to that IP Address (such as domain information, your internet provider and general geographic location);
  * Browsing history on our site (such as what you search for, the pages you view, how long you stay, and how often you come back);
  * How you search for our site, from which sites you visit to our site, and which of our Business Partners' sites you visit;
  * Which ads or online content from us and our Business Partners you view, access, or click on;
  * Whether you open our electronic communications and which parts you click on 
  * The location of your mobile device (for example, when you use our mobile sites or apps to register to receive location-based content).

We (and our Service Providers or Third-Party Ad-Servers) also may collect information made publicly available through third-party platforms (such as social media sites), online databases or other directories. 

## How do we use the information we collect about you?

We may use Online Information we collect about you on its own or combine it with Other Information we have about you to:

  * Deliver products and services, including to:
    * recognize you when you return to our sites;
    * complete transactions; 
    * tell you about updates to your membership, products, and services;
    * answer questions and respond to your requests made through our sites and through third-party sites (including social media); 
    * improve our sites and make them easier to use; 
  * Use the location of your mobile device to prevent fraud or deliver other location-based services that you may request;
  * Protect your information;
  * Update you about new features and benefits; 
  * Determine how to best provide services to you, such as the best way to contact you;
  * Advertise and market our products and services - and those of our Business Partners \- including to:
    * present Targeted Advertising send or provide you with ads, promotions, and offers;
    * analyze whether our ads, promotions, and offers are effective; 
    * help us determine whether you may be interested in new products or services; 
  * Conduct research and analysis, including to:
    * better understand our customers and site visitors;
    * allow you to give feedback by rating and reviewing our products and services and those of our Business Partners; 
    * produce data analytics, statistical research, and reports; 
    * review and change our products and services;
  * Use it in other ways as required or permitted by law or with your consent.

## Your California Privacy Rights: Notice to California Customers

California's "Shine the Light" law, Civil Code Section 1798.83, requires certain businesses to respond to requests from California customers asking about the businesses' practices related to disclosing personal information to third parties for the third parties' direct marketing purposes. Alternately, such businesses may have in place a policy not to disclose personal information of customers to third parties for the third parties' direct marketing purposes if the customer has exercised an option to opt-out of such information-sharing. (Note: TIAMG sites do not recognize the "do not track signals" that some browsers may employ.) As discussed above, if you wish to opt-out of our sharing of your information with third parties for the third parties' direct marketing purposes offline please click here, or for email please click here. To find out more about your opt-out rights, please contact us as described in the "How to Contact Us" section below.

Some Online Information and Other Information is Personal Information, which is information that can identify a person, such as name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, date of birth and credit or debit card information.

## How we treat your Personal Information

We do not share Personal Information with anyone except as described below. We may share Personal Information as required or as permitted by law, such as:

  * With regulatory authorities, courts, and governmental agencies to comply with legal orders, legal or regulatory requirements, and government requests;
  * With our Service Providers, regulatory authorities, and governmental agencies to detect and prevent fraud or criminal activity, and to protect the rights of TIAMG or others;
  * Within the other divisions of Time Inc. Affluent Media Group that share this privacy policy;
  * With our Service Providers who perform services for us and help us operate our business (we require Service Providers to safeguard Personal Information and only use your Personal Information for the purposes we specify);
  * With Business Partners who may wish to contact you about products, services, and offers that may interest you, either in conjunction with TIAMG or by themselves. These Business Partners' practices are not covered by this privacy policy. (If you do not want us to share your Personal Information with our Business Partners in the future, please click here.);
  * In the context of a sale of all or part of Time Inc. Affluent Media Group or or their assets; or
  * For specific products or services, when you have given your consent.
  * Also, we may transfer Personal Information to Service Providers or companies within the Time Inc. Affluent Media Group throughout the world, for example, to process transactions and provide you with our products or services. Regardless of where we process your information, we still protect it in the manner described in this privacy policy and according to the applicable laws.

## How we handle Aggregate and De-Identified Information

Aggregate Information or De-Identified Information does not identify you individually; it helps us to analyze patterns among groups of people. We may share Aggregate Information or De-Identified Information in several ways, for example:

  * For the same reasons as we might share Personal Information;
  * With Business Partners to help develop and market products and deliver targeted content and ads;
  * With Business Partners to conduct analysis and research about customers and site visitors; or
  * With Third-Party Ad-Servers to place ads (including ads of our Business Partners) on various sites and applications, and to analyze the effectiveness of those ads.

Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we cannot assure you that personally identifiable information that we collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Policy. Inadvertent disclosures may result, for example, when third parties misrepresent their identities in asking the site for access to personally identifiable information about themselves for purposes of correcting possible factual errors in the data.

## How do we keep and safeguard your information?

We use administrative, technical and physical security measures to protect your Personal Information. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and facilities. No system can be completely secure, however, and we do not guarantee that unauthorized disclosures and access will not happen.

We will keep your Online Information and Other Information as long as necessary to deliver our products and services, unless we are required by law or regulation or for litigation and regulatory investigations to keep it for a longer period of time.

## What are your choices?

You have choices about how TIAMG uses your information, such as how we market to you or how we manage Cookies or Similar Technologies[1].

## What are your choices about how we directly market to you?

You can choose how you would like to receive direct marketing communications - whether we send them to you through postal mail, email and/or telephone. If you choose to not receive marketing communications from us, we will honor your choice. Please be aware that if you choose not to receive such communications, certain offers attached to the products or services you have chosen may be affected. We will still communicate with you in connection with servicing your account, fulfilling your requests, or administering any promotion or any program in which you have elected to participate.

## Collection of Information by Third-Party Sites and Sponsors

Some of our sites contain links to other sites whose information practices may be different than ours. You should consult the other sites' and services' privacy notices, as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties or their use of your information.

TIAMG sites sometimes may offer contests, sweepstakes, promotions, editorial features, or other activities or offerings that are sponsored or co-sponsored by or presented with identified third parties. By virtue of your participation in such activities or offerings, your IP address and the personally identifiable information that you voluntarily submit may be provided to both the TIAMG site and the third parties. TIAMG has no control over the third parties' use of this information.

## How we serve advertising

We use reputable third parties to serve advertisements, including Online Behavioral Advertisements, that you may see on the web pages and to conduct research about the advertisements. This privacy notice does not cover any use of information that such third parties may have collected from you (e.g., type of browser, operating system, domain name, day and time of visit, page(s) visited) or the methods used by the third-parties to collect that information (e.g., cookies, web beacons and clear gifs). 

For additional information on advertisements and your Online Behavioral Advertising options, visit our [About Ads page](http://www.amexpub.com/privacy/amg-behavioral.html) and our [Network Advertising Initiatives page](http://subscription-assets.timeinc.com/prod/assets/themes/magazines/default/template-resources/html/legal/parties.html). 

## Accessing, Correcting, and Deleting Your Personal Information

We will take reasonable steps to accurately record the personal information that you provide to us and any subsequent updates.

We encourage you to review and update the personal information that we maintain about you, and you may request that we delete personal information about you that is inaccurate or incomplete by contacting us as described in the "How to Contact Us" section below. At our election, instead of deleting such information, we may retain it with your comment or correction noted in our records. Your right to review, update, correct and delete your information is subject to our records retention policies and applicable law, including any statutory retention requirements.

If you have questions about our online privacy policy, you may contact us by 1-866-642-1356 or write to us at

Time Inc. Affluent Media Group  
Attention: Consumer Affairs  
3000 University Center Drive  
Tampa, Florida 33612-6408

[Click here](mailto:privacy@timeinc.com) to email us if you have any questions about our online privacy policy. 

**Aggregate Information** \- data or information relating to multiple people which has been combined or aggregated. Aggregate Information includes information that we create or compile from various sources, including subscriptions or certain data from Cookies and Similar Technologies. 

**Time Inc. Affluent Media Group ("we," "our," "us"),** a subsidiary of Time Inc.. All rights reserved. 

**Business Partners** \- any third parties with whom we conduct business and have a contractual relationship, such as a business that advertises on our sites, applications or within our products. 

**Cookies and Similar Technologies** \- A _cookie_ is a small data file that a website transfers to your computer's hard drive. We may send cookies when you visit our site or sites where our ads appear or when you make purchases, request or personalize information, or register for certain services. If you accept the cookies used on our site, sites that are â€œpowered byâ€ another company on our behalf, or sites where our ads appear, you may give us access to information about your interests. We may use that information to personalize your experience. Similar technologies such as web beacons, pixels, gifs, and tags also do the same thing. We use the term _Cookies and Similar Technologies_ in this policy to refer to all technologies that collect information in this way. 

Most browsers automatically accept cookies. You can set your browser option so that you will not receive cookies, and you can also delete existing cookies from your browser. However, you may find that some parts of the site will not function properly if you have refused Cookies and Similar Technologies. If you wish to block cookies, go to <http://www.allaboutcookies.org/> to find out how, or check your browser's instructions. 

**De-identified Information** \- data or information used in a way that does not identify you to a third party. We often derive De-Identified Information from Personal Information. It includes information that we may collect from various sources, such as subscriptions or certain data from Cookies and Similar Technologies.

**IP Address** \- a number assigned to a device when connecting to the Internet. 

**Service Providers** \- any vendor, third party and/or company that performs business operations on our behalf, such as printing, mailing, and other communications services (email, direct mail, etc.), marketing, data processing, servicing, collections, or ad management.

**Targeted Advertising** \- Ads that we, or our Service Providers, display on our sites and outside the Time Inc. Affluent Media Group based on the preferences or interests inferred from data collected from a particular computer or device regarding web viewing behaviors over time and across different websites.

**Third-Party Ad-Servers** \- companies that provide the technology to place ads on sites and mobile applications and track how ads perform. These companies may also place and access cookies on your computer and device. The information they collect from our sites is in a form that does not identify you personally.

© 2020 Time Inc. Affluent Media Group. A part of the Time.com sites. All rights reserved.
